<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>reality on Rizwan Hasan</title>
    <link>https://rizwan.studio/philosophy/tags/reality/</link>
    <description>Recent content in reality on Rizwan Hasan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rizwan.studio/philosophy/tags/reality/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Philosophy of Independency</title>
      <link>https://rizwan.studio/philosophy/posts/philosophy-of-independency/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rizwan.studio/philosophy/posts/philosophy-of-independency/</guid>
      <description>To become independent you’ve to learn how to become dependent. Because independency comes from dependency. Also, independence is not a constant thing. Everyone depends on another for something. Like if you hadn’t depended on your parents for those years maybe you won’t able to read these lines you’re reading now. Independence means shifting dependency according to the situation. If your way of dependent is flexible; congratulation; you’re independent now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philosophy of Seeing Parents</title>
      <link>https://rizwan.studio/philosophy/posts/philosophy-of-seeing-parents/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rizwan.studio/philosophy/posts/philosophy-of-seeing-parents/</guid>
      <description>Your parents are not your god. You’re the outcome of their love but believing them as god will be foolishness because God assigned them for you to give you a chance so that you can become an independent person. Independency comes from dependency. You’ve to be dependent on your parents for a certain time and at the same time have to figure out a way that best suits you to achieve independence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philosophy of Love and Desire</title>
      <link>https://rizwan.studio/philosophy/posts/philosophy-of-love-and-desire/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rizwan.studio/philosophy/posts/philosophy-of-love-and-desire/</guid>
      <description>People often misunderstand their desires and try to justify them with love. Just observe and see how desperate they are. Expecting love from them is foolishness because desire leads to desperateness where love creates flexibility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philosophy of Yes and No</title>
      <link>https://rizwan.studio/philosophy/posts/philosophy-of-yes-and-no/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rizwan.studio/philosophy/posts/philosophy-of-yes-and-no/</guid>
      <description>Not every time you need to give a conclusion with Yes or No. The same goes for expectation also. Yes and No are just a bunch of labels we believe. There&amp;rsquo;s also a state that exists between them, filled with countless happiness. If you can able to observe, just see; you&amp;rsquo;re getting it already or maybe much more than your expectation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philosophy of People&#39;s Compliment</title>
      <link>https://rizwan.studio/philosophy/posts/philosophy-of-peoples-compliment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rizwan.studio/philosophy/posts/philosophy-of-peoples-compliment/</guid>
      <description>You must not count every compliment you get. Most people don&amp;rsquo;t know how to give a compliment. If you observe well, you&amp;rsquo;ll see it&amp;rsquo;s just their normal way of talking to others. They&amp;rsquo;re just telling you that they can&amp;rsquo;t or they don&amp;rsquo;t want to do the thing that they are complementing on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philosophy of World&#39;s Reality</title>
      <link>https://rizwan.studio/philosophy/posts/philosophy-of-worlds-reality/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rizwan.studio/philosophy/posts/philosophy-of-worlds-reality/</guid>
      <description>The world has become a very strange place for good people. People don&amp;rsquo;t want to make compromises but expect from others by showing their kind of relationship label. It&amp;rsquo;s a very strange behavior of them and disrespectful also.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
